http://www.nanophase.com/not-nav/privacy/

1.630.771.6700 |
HomeAbout Us
+Contact UsManagement Team
+Board of DirectorsNews and EventsRelated LinksCareersHistoryMarkets
+Personal CarePlasticsTextilesExterior CoatingsIntegrated Circuit and Data StorageOptical Surface PolishingEnergyProducts
+Antimony Tin OxideBismuth OxideCerium OxideIron OxideZinc OxideTechnology
+Nanoparticle Production TechnologyNanoparticle Surface TreatmentDispersion TechnologyQuality/EH&S
+Quality SystemsManufacturing ExcellenceLean 6 SigmaEH&S Information
+CONEGEnvironmental ResponsibilityNanomaterial SafetyNanotechnology Standardization InitiativeOccupational SafetyREACHRoHSTSCASDS Request
Investor Relations
+Annual ReportsInvestor News
+2020 Q3 Financial ResultsLaura M. Beres Joins Nanophase Board of Directors2020 Q2 Financial Results2020 Q1 Financial ResultsNanophase Receives Funding Under Paycheck Protection Program2019 Q4 Financial Results2019 Q3 Financial Results2019 Q2 Financial Results2019 Second Quarter Conference Call2019 Q1 Financial Results2019 First Quarter Conference Call2018 Q4 Financial Results2018 Fourth Quarter Conference Call2018 Q3 Financial Results2018 Third Quarter Conference Call2018 Q2 Financial Results2018 Second Quarter Conference Call2018 Q1 Financial Results2017 Q4 Financial ResultsNanophase Announces New Chief Financial Officer2017 Year End Conference Call2017 Q3 Financial Results2017 Third Quarter Conference Call2017 Shareholder Presentation2017 Q2 Financial Results2017 Second Quarter Conference CallNanophase Announces Strategic Collaboration2017 Q1 Financial Results2017 First Quarter Conference Call2016 Year End Conference Call2016 Q4 Financial Results2016 Q3 Financial Results2016 Q3 Conference Call2016 Shareholder Presentation2016 Q2 Financial Results2016 Q2 Conference Call2016 Q1 Financial Results2016 Q1 Conference Call2015 Q4 Financial Results2015 Year End Conference Call2015 Q3 Financial Results2015 Q3 Conference Call2015 Q2 Financial Results2015 Q2 Conference Call2015 Q1 Financial Results2015 Q1 Conference Call2014 Q4 Financial Results2014 Year End Conference Call2014 Q3 Financials2014 Q3 Conference Call2014 Q2 Financials2014 Q2 Conference Call2014 Q1 Financials2013 Q4 Financials2013 Year End Conference Call2013 Q3 Financials2013 Q3 Conference Call2011 Q3 Conference Call2011 Q1 Conference Call2009 Q3 Conference Call2008 Year End Financials2009 Q1 Conference CallConference Call Transcripts
+2019 Q32019 Q22019 Q12018 Q4 & YE2018 Q32018 Q12017 Q42017 Q32017 Q22017 Q12016 Q42016 Q32016 Q22016 Q12015 Q42015 Q32015 Q22015 Q12014 Q42014 Q32014 Q22014 Q12013 Q42013 Q32013 Q22013 Q12012 Q42012 Q32012 Q22012 Q12011 Q42011 Q32011 Q22011 Q12010 Q42010 Q32010 Q22010 Q12009 Q42009 Q32009 Q22009 Q12008 Q42008 Q3Information RequestSEC FilingsStock QuoteCorporate GovernanceConflict Minerals Disclosure
NANOPHASE TECHNOLOGIES CORPORATION PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy explains the information that Nanophase Technologies Corporation (“Nanophase,” “Company,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) collects on www.Nanophase.com (the Web Site), how we use your information collected at the Web Site and your choices related to our data collection practices on the Web Site. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Please also read our Terms of Use, which governs your use of the Web Site. Your use of the Web Site indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please note that this Privacy Policy only covers information collection practices on the Web Site and does not cover any information collected offline by us or at any other web site.
Information Collected
We may ask you to provide us with personally identifiable information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally (such as your name, address, or e-mail address) when you are on the Web Site, such as when you register with us, if you agree to receive e-mails from us, you contact us with a question, or you submit a resume. We may, at any time, add features to the Web Site that also require you to register or otherwise provide personally identifiable information. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in some or all of the Web Site’s features. This Web Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.
In addition to the above, when you visit or download information from this Site, our web servers may automatically collect web site usage information. Web site usage information is non-personally identifiable information that describes how our visitors use and navigate this Site. It can include the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays, browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting the Site, and IP address (see below for more information on IP addresses). We may determine the applicable technology available in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page, e-mail or similar service.
Use of Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses
An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer or network when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from this Web Site, our servers log your IP address. We may use IP addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the use of the Web Site. We may associate your IP address with the personally identifiable information you provide. We may also use IP addresses in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies to identify users if we deem it necessary to comply with law, to enforce compliance with its Privacy Policy or this Web Site’s Terms of Use, or to protect the Web Site or its users.
USE OF COOKIES
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site either transfers to your computer’s hard drive or stores temporarily in your computer’s memory for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as to recognize registered users and their access privileges, as well as to track site usage and maintain security of the user’s account. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent by indicating this in the preferences or options menu in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of this Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies and you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of this Site. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.
Use and Disclosure of Information Collected at the Site
Use
We may use your personally identifiable information to answer a question or provide you with requested information concerning our products and services, to send you e-mail updates on our behalf or on behalf of our external business partners or affiliates, for internal business purposes, to contact you regarding your use of the Web Site or changes to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, or for other purposes disclosed at the time you submit your information.
Disclosure/Sharing
Nanophase does not share the personally identifiable information collected through the Web Site with third parties except as set forth in this Privacy Policy and:
In response to judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena, or a request from local, state or federal law enforcement officials or other governmental authorities conducting an investigation;
When the Company employs third parties to perform functions on its behalf, which may include, without limitation, third party hosting companies, communication services (including e-mail and mail), data analysts and other customer service companies; and
In the event Company merges with another business entity or its assets related to the products or services that you receive from Company are acquired by another business entity, or its business is consolidated, or it goes through a fundamental corporate change.
We may also disclose non-personally identifying information, such as aggregated user statistics to third parties for several reasons, including, without limitation, obtaining advertisers and describing us and the Web Site to third parties.
YOUR CHOICES (How to Change Your INFORMATION)
You may edit your registration profile by logging in with your user id and password. Once logged in, you may edit your contact information or change your user id and password. If you decide that you no longer wish to receive e-mail from us, you may unsubscribe from this service by selecting "Join Mailing List” under “Contact Us,” and selecting “unsubscribe.” You can also unsubscribe through the mechanism provided in an e-mail you receive from us.
If you have difficulty unsubscribing through our web site or if you have other privacy questions, please contact us by email or in writing at the following location:
Nanophase Technologies CorporationAttn: Privacy Manager1319 Marquette DriveRomeoville, IL 60446U.S.A. E-mail: privacy@nanophase.com
Please be aware that we will process your request as quickly as we reasonably can, but it may not be possible to update our systems immediately. You should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases.
Security
We use reasonable safeguards to protect Personally Identifiable Information we collect on this Site from unauthorized access, use, modification or disclosure. However, due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside of our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.
Consent to Transfer
This Site is operated in the United States. If you are located in Canada, the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to Nanophase will be transferred to the United States. By using this Site, participating in any of the Company’s services or providing Company with your information, you consent to this transfer.
Links
While on the Web Site or viewing an e-mail or other content provided by Nanophase or the Web Site, you may encounter links to other web sites or online materials operated by third parties. If you click on a link to such a third party, the click takes you off the Web Site and to a third party’s web site, which is beyond Nanophase’s control. These other web sites may set their own cookies (there is information above about cookies), collect data or have their own privacy policies and practices. As noted above, this Privacy Policy only covers information collected by the Company on this Web Site, and we encourage you to review the privacy policy of any other web site you visit. Links to any third party web site or content do not constitute or imply an endorsement or recommendation by Nanophase of the linked web site or content.
Acceptance & PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
By using this Site, you accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any new or revised policies on the Web Site, but we will only use your personally identifiable information in accordance with the privacy policy that was in effect at the time it was collected, unless you consent to any new terms regarding its use.
This Company Privacy Policy has an effective date of June 15, 2009.
© 2020 Nanophase Technologies Corporation.1319 Marquette Dr, Romeoville, IL 60446 | 1.630.771.6700
terms of use | standard terms & conditions | privacy | sitemap
